[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_046",
        "question": "A 60-year-old man presents with rapidly growing lesions on his face, trunk, axillae, flexural areas, and groin. <br>- The lesions appeared 3 months earlier in his perianal area and extended rapidly to other areas. <br>- Previously, he was treated with topical agents for atopic dermatitis and seborrheic dermatitis without improvement. <br>- Examination reveals disseminated violaceous papules and plaques on the face, trunk, axillae, and perianal area; some lesions were confluent and ulcerated. <br>- Yellowish-red to skin-colored papules are present on the scalp. <br>- He has no palpable lymphadenopathy or organomegaly.",
        "option1": "Atopic dermatitis",
        "option2": "Prurigo nodularis",
        "option3": "Cutaneous Langerhans cell histiocytosis",
        "option4": "Seborrheic dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_138",
        "question": "A 34-year-old woman presents with complaints of a severely itchy rash affecting both lower legs that developed three days ago after returning from camping six days ago. <br>- She reports during the camping trip they often hiked for several hours a day, and she wore shorts due to the humid, hot weather. <br>- When the rash began, it began as small red bumps that formed larger fluid filled bumps. <br>- She has tried over the counter cortisone that helps with the itch a little bit. <br>- She denies any new topical lotions, laundry detergents, or body washes. <br>-   Physical exam reveals multiple streaks of yellow vesicles on bright pink erythematous bases in a linear distribution on the bilateral lower extremities.",
        "option1": "Irritant contact dermatitis",
        "option2": "Poison ivy allergic contact dermatitis",
        "option3": "Nummular eczema",
        "option4": "Scabies",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "51%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_118",
        "question": "A 22-year-old male presents with a follicular eruption that has been present for 2 weeks. <br>- He has a history of anorexia nervosa and alcoholism. <br>- There is no identifiable preceding incident related to the eruption. <br>- He denies a history of atopy, drug use, and new medications. <br>- A review of systems shows positive findings for joint pain and bleeding gums. <br>- Physical exam reveals ecchymosis and purpuric follicular papules with corkscrew-like hair on his legs and arms.",
        "option1": "IgA vasculitis",
        "option2": "Scurvy",
        "option3": "Thrombocytopenic purpura",
        "option4": "Chronic liver disease",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "44%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_023",
        "question": "The patient is a 12-year-old Hispanic girl who presents with a 6-month history of nail dystrophy involving all of her fingernails. <br>- On examination, all 10 of her fingernails exhibit longitudinal ridging, pitting, fragility, thinning, and distal notching. <br>- The patient’s mother is very concerned about the cosmesis of her daughter’s nails. <br>- The patient has no systemic symptoms. <br>- On review of systems, the patient’s mother noted that her daughter has started to develop circular patches of hair loss that appear to resolve on their own. <br>- The patient has no relevant social or family history and does not take any medications.",
        "option1": "Brittle nails",
        "option2": "Lichen planus",
        "option3": "Psoriasis",
        "option4": "Trachyonychia",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "70%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_025",
        "question": "An 8-year-old African-American boy presents with a 3-day history of fever, pain, and a rash on his trunk. <br>- On examination, the patient has several fragile, bullous lesions on his trunk, many of which have eroded, exposing erythematous, annular lesions. <br>- The patient is febrile and shaking in the office, and he appears to be in pain. <br>- He has no other relevant social or family history and does not take any medications. <br>- His mother is very concerned about her son.",
        "option1": "Stevens-Johnson syndrome",
        "option2": "Bullous impetigo",
        "option3": "Autoimmune bullous dermatoses",
        "option4": "Bullous erythema multiforme",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "70%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_033",
        "question": "On day-of-life 2, a 3-day-old boy who was born with no visible skin problems begins to develop erosions and bullae over both the palmar and plantar surfaces. <br>- These bullae are localized to areas of friction or trauma (eg, where electrocardiogram leads were placed). <br>- The mother’s pregnancy was normal, and the infant had been born without complications. <br>- Aside from the development of bullae, the infant has no evidence of any other medical problems. <br>- The infant’s parents are healthy and have no medical problems. <br>- No one in the infant’s family has had similar dermatologic findings.",
        "option1": "Herpes",
        "option2": "Staphylococcal infection",
        "option3": "Epidermolysis bullosa",
        "option4": "Bullous impetigo",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "65%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_081",
        "question": "A 15-year-old girl presents with patches of hair loss on her scalp that have been present for the last 6 months. <br>- She reports that her scalp is not itchy or painful and denies any recent illnesses, diet changes, or stressful life events. <br>- She does not have any other medical conditions and takes no medications. <br>- Her uncle had a similar condition that started when he was in his 20s, but no one else in the family has experienced hair loss. <br>- The patient says she has not tried any treatments for the condition. <br>- On examination, she has several well-demarcated patches of hair loss on her frontal and parietal scalp, with no perifollicular erythema or scale.",
        "option1": "Tinea capitis",
        "option2": "Androgenetic alopecia",
        "option3": "Trichotillomania",
        "option4": "Alopecia areata",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_022",
        "question": "A 42-year-old man presents with a four-day history of experiencing headache, malaise, and stabbing right-sided headache. <br>- Two days after his initial symptoms appeared, he developed a rash over the area of pain. <br>- He reports that he went hiking through the Texas hill country prior to becoming ill. <br>- The patient is otherwise in good health and has an unremarkable medical history. <br>- Physical examination reveals unilateral erythematous, thin, raised plaques over the right forehead. <br>- In addition, he has no relevant social or family history.",
        "option1": "Scabies",
        "option2": "Contact dermatitis",
        "option3": "Zosteriform herpes simplex",
        "option4": "Herpes zoster",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "83%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_093",
        "question": "A 28-year-old Black man presents with a 2-year history of dyspigmentation of his back and chest. <br>- The patient notes that the lesions initially had red borders but these have faded over the past several months. <br>- Physical examination reveals circular, ashy-gray macules distributed diffusely over his back and chest. <br>- The patient denies pain or pruritus and takes nomedication. <br>- He notes that he recently traveled to Mexico. <br>- He has been relatively unconcerned about the lesions and only sought medical care to rule out cancer.",
        "option1": "Addison disease",
        "option2": "Erythema dyschromicum perstans",
        "option3": "Fixed-drug eruption",
        "option4": "Macular amyloidosis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "73%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_059",
        "question": "A 48-year-old premenopausal woman, who has had one pregnancy and has delivered once, presents with a 15-month history of left breast deformity. <br>- The patient began having pain in the region 2 months ago. <br>- A review of systems is negative for weight loss, fever, or nipple discharge. <br>- Her medical history is otherwise unremarkable, and her family history is noncontributory. <br>- Physical examination is notable for extensive left nipple inversion and retraction, a large underlying mass in the central breast, edema and ulceration of the overlying skin of the breast, and matted ipsilateral axillary nodes. <br>- There is no erythema of the skin. <br>- The right breast is unremarkable.",
        "option1": "Duct ectasia",
        "option2": "Congenital nipple inversion",
        "option3": "Periductal mastitis",
        "option4": "Nipple inversion secondary to neglected malignancy",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "43%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_004",
        "question": "A 20-year-old woman presents to the clinic with a circular hypopigmented lesion on her right cheek. <br>- The patient stated that she used to have a mole in the same location. <br>- Over time she noticed a white area around the mole that enlarged to the current size of the lesion. <br>- After a few months she noticed the mole in the center of the lesion had disappeared. <br>- On further questioning, she denies any personal or family history of skin cancer.",
        "option1": "Dysplastic nevus",
        "option2": "Vitiligo",
        "option3": "Melanoma",
        "option4": "Halo nevus",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "76%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_027",
        "question": "A 52-year-old Hispanic woman presents with a 3-year history of a very pruritic rash over her shins bilaterally. <br>- On examination, both shins are covered in hyperpigmented papules that have coalesced to form thin, rippled plaques. <br>- The patient is very concerned about the appearance of her legs and the intense pruritus in the areas of the rash. <br>- The patient has no other medical problems and has no systemic symptoms. <br>- She has no relevant social or family history and does not take any medications.",
        "option1": "Lichen amyloidosis",
        "option2": "Hypertrophic lichen planus",
        "option3": "Pretibial myxedema",
        "option4": "Prurigo nodularis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_107",
        "question": "A 25-year-old male presents with 6 months of discoloration in the underarms. <br>- He denies any blisters or erosions in the areas. <br>- He denies any history of diabetes, insulin resistance, or weight gain. <br>- He denies itch. <br>- He denies discoloration only with sweating. <br>- Physical examination reveals reddish-brown patches in the underarms; Wood's lamp reveals coral red fluorescence.",
        "option1": "Hailey-Hailey Disease",
        "option2": "Erythrasma",
        "option3": "Acanthosis nigricans",
        "option4": "Inverse psoriasis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_019",
        "question": "The patient is a 21-year-old male who presents for continued acne therapy. <br>- He has had severe acne on his face, chest, and back for years. <br>- He is happy with his current acne regimen of topical tretinoin, topical clindamycin, and oral minocycline. <br>- He has been on the regimen for years. <br>- On examination, you notice significant blue-black discoloration confined to sites of previous acne scars. <br>- The patient has no other medical problems and no relevant social or family history.",
        "option1": "Type I minocycline hyperpigmentation",
        "option2": "Type III minocycline hyperpigmentation",
        "option3": "Type II minocycline hyperpigmentation",
        "option4": "Immunobullous disease",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "80%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_135",
        "question": "A 5-year-old boy presents to the pediatrician office with complaints of multiple spots that began on the abdomen and spread to the arms and legs. <br>- The spots are not itchy or painful, unless he scratches them. <br>- Sometimes the skin surronding the lesion will become very red and painful, but then the lesion and redness fade. <br>- The parents report they have tried topical corticosteroids but the lesions do not go away. <br>-   Mom endorses a history of atopic dermatitis in her sister and herself. <br>-   Physical exam reveals multiple dome shaped skin colored to light pink papules with central umbilication and yellow core across the chest and back.",
        "option1": "Molluscum contagiosum",
        "option2": "Basal cell carcinoma",
        "option3": "Herpes virus infection",
        "option4": "Fibrous papule",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]